A sound soul dwells within a sound mind and a sound body.
Hey, Krona, good morning.
Oh, good morning.
Come on, let's get going.
See you in your dreams, yeah, baby.
Oh, good morning.
I am forever with you so
見上がれば輝く
月のように
and may be
you.
yeah
come on corno quit hiding
there's nothing to be afraid of here
Why?
Why is everybody so nice to me?
Why do they go out of their way to help me?
Why?
Good ass!
Good job, Gruner!
Take it away from him!
Come on, Gruner, you can do it!
Looks like things are starting to get better for him.
Yeah, it's slow going, but we're working on it.
So, Sol, how have you been doing?
Huh?
That wound you took in the chest.
Ah, it's fine.
Anyway, dwelling too much on the past ain't cool.
Especially when it comes to a fight we ended up losing.
You can just forget like that?
Maka's been working hard with Krona.
I don't want to spoil that by dredging up any bad memories.
I get it.
All right.
Let's get in on this.
Here!
Give me that a sec.
Your center of gravity is high, see?
You need to bend your knees a little more.
Relax your shoulders and then throw.
Here, you give it a try.
I think it's time for another party.
Drying happiness.
Whose tears sparkle in the moonlight?
Hey, Sol, thanks for contributing to the music selection.
Sure.
Is this one going to be okay, though?
Well, you said to bring something catchy, so I decided on this punk record.
But it might not work that well for this crowd.
Yeah.
Well then, play the piano.
There's one right there.
Why the sudden craving?
It's been a while since I've heard you.
I think I'll pass on that one.
I gotta take a leak.
Aw, he got away.
I had no idea he could play the piano.
Yeah, he's only played for me once, though.
Right before we first became partners.
What kind of song?
It's hard to explain.
Something dark and strange.
He said, this is the kind of person I am, and just started playing.
Something about that song and the way he played it must have gotten to me.
And we became partners.
Hm.
Well, I'm sorry I missed it.
Shibatsu!
Seconds!
Give me seconds!
Yeah, okay.
Sorry, Krona.
A noisy group like this must make you uncomfortable.
I'm not completely used to it yet.
But I'm not feeling uncomfortable either.
No one's going anywhere for a bit.
So you can take your time.
Join the group at your own pace.
Hm?
There's no need to rush this sort of thing.
Yo!
What are you hanging out over here for?
It's a party.
Let's have some fun!
What was that for?
Don't bully Krona.
What's up?
Someone's bullying Krona?
Krona, if someone's giving you a hard time, you just let old Blackstar know.
I'll throw him out the nearest window.
Why is everyone so nice to someone like me?
It's simple, Krona.
That's just what friends do.
If you're a friend, then feed me!
Here!
Shibaki made it herself!
I sure hope you enjoy it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Gross.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha!
Krona, come and hang out at my place next time.
I don't mind cooking.
It's worth it for someone with an appetite as big as Ragnarok's is.
See you later, then.
Bye-bye!
I'll see you tomorrow.
Hey, Krona!
You should try to find a partner who can cook like that Tsubaki girl!
How can I do that?
I thought you were already my partner.
The party was a lot of fun, wasn't it?
The food was good, at least.
I've been waiting for you.
Hi, Krona.
Lady Medusa.
Very good, Krona.
I wasn't sure you'd recognize me in this sad state.
Embarrassing, isn't it?
You've gotten all tiny, just like me!
W-why?
Why are you back in Death City?
I came for you, Krona.
I've been so worried about you.
You're worried?
Does that mean you're here to bring me back with you?
Oh, no.
You should stay in the academy and continue your work as my spy.
Oh, what are you talking about?
A spy?
Me?
There's no need to be so modest about it.
That's why you infiltrated the DWMA, right?
To become a spy?
You did a good job, but now I have a task only you can do.
There's a secret vault somewhere within the academy.
For now, all I need you to do is find it.
I'm counting on you, Krona.
No, wait!
I've made some friends at the academy.
Doing this might make them angry at me.
But you'll do it, won't you?
For your dear mother.
Yes, ma'am.
I understand.
Gooby-bee!
Things are getting interesting.
Death City is growing thick with madness.
It won't be long before something happens.
Folk music grows.
You're joking, right?
Tell me you're joking.
I didn't ask for your opinion.
Seriously, though.
How can you listen to that?
Folk music is stupid.
I may not do very well on tests, but even I know that much, dude.
I listen to whatever I want.
Leave me alone.
Krona?
Oh, sorry.
I think I'll head back to my room now.
See you tomorrow.
We'll see ya.
What's wrong with him?
He's been more withdrawn than usual lately.
Really?
How can you tell the difference?
You'd better get moving, or Medusa won't be happy.
Good to see you, Justin.
How are things?
Hey, Spirit, give me a hand.
Justin's got his headphones in as usual,
and he can't read my lips with this mask on.
Do me a favor and repeat everything I say
for the rest of the conversation.
Cool.
What, am I some kind of parrot now?
Can't he just take out the headphones?
Okay, now repeat after me.
Justin, I called you into the death room today
because I need to explain the new assignment I'm giving you.
Hey, hold on.
These are your orders from Lord Death.
Listen up.
The reason you were called in here today
is to receive your latest assignment.
Okay?
What is it?
This is a very important mission.
You're aware that because of her extraordinary scouting abilities,
Azusa has been given the task of hunting down the Kishin?
You know Azusa's the one in charge of hunting down the Kishin, right?
But there's a limit to what she can do from here.
That's why I need you to help.
While she's using her eyes,
I want you to use your legs.
Travel everywhere searching for the Kishin.
But she can only do so much with her eyes.
That's where you come in.
You're gonna be her legs.
Hey, that's not what I said.
Repeat it properly from now on.
You're taking too long to explain it.
Say that again.
Yeah, fine.
I got it.
Now then.
Here's what I'm hoping will happen.
If you can make enough noise during your search,
you may be able to flush out the Cowardly Kishin
from wherever it's hiding.
Do you understand the assignment?
Here's what I'm hoping will happen.
If you can make enough noise during your search,
you may be able to flush out the Cowardly Kishin
from wherever it's hiding.
Do you understand the assignment?
Oh, what a truly wondrous assignment!
I accept the mission with great pleasure.
I'm counting on you to succeed.
Right.
Looks like the hallway's off-limits from here.
Go beep-beep!
Which might mean it's a good place to look for the vault.
What if somebody sees me wandering down here?
What am I supposed to do then?
It's not my problem if you get yourself caught.
Hello?
Who's there?
Oh, it's you, Krona.
What are you doing?
You shouldn't be down here, you know.
This area's off-limits.
Um, I, uh...
Well, I...
You saved us, Marie!
We were trying to find our room,
and we lost our way!
Well, I'm actually a little lost myself.
The Academy's layout is confusing.
I still don't understand it.
But we'll figure it out somehow.
Just leave it to me.
Don't worry.
I'll help you find your room.
Now, let's see here.
It's this way!
You sure about that?
Well, we made it.
Thanks a lot.
We couldn't have done it without you.
If you run into any more difficulties,
don't hesitate to let me know, okay?
I'll be glad to help.
Except with directions.
I'll leave you here then.
Good night!
The teacher's office is that way.
Ribbit.
I hate this.
I can't stand going back and forth
from such a dangerous place.
Erica...
What's your progress?
Do you know where the secret vault is?
I can't do this.
I can't deal with this kind of situation.
That isn't what we wanted to hear, Crona.
Right, Lady Medusa?
It's okay.
You're doing very well, Crona.
How about this?
I'll give you a different mission instead.
Tell me how Professor Stein's been doing.
I don't see him very often,
so I'm not sure how much I can tell you about him.
From what I can tell,
he started partnering with Miss Marie,
and they're living together now.
Marie?
What's she like?
She's gentle and kind.
She's friendly to everybody,
and she always looks out for me.
Hmm.
Is that so?
All right.
Let's make use of that sweet nature of hers.
Have a good day, Miss Marie.
You too.
See you tomorrow.
Miss Marie?
Yes?
Is something wrong, Crona?
Uh, it's just that...
Can I help you with something?
Well, yes.
Actually, I...
There's something I wanted to talk to you.
Goodbye, Miss Marie.
Oh, have a good afternoon, girls.
I have an idea.
Why don't you come to my house?
We can talk over some tea.
Oh, okay.
There's a tiny listening device
hidden inside the pen.
All you have to do is place it
in Professor Stein's laboratory.
Here you go.
This place didn't have anything
but beakers and test tubes
when I got here.
I had to bring the cups in myself.
These are very nice cups.
Who cares as long as you can drink from it?
Looks like you have added
your own girly touch here and there.
I can't bring in too much stuff
or Stein will throw a fit.
But I'm adjusting little by little.
So tell me what it is
that's been troubling you.
Oh, you see...
I, uh...
Hey!
Why didn't I get any?
I'm thirsty, too!
Uh, Ragnarok can drink,
but he doesn't have a mouth, does he?
Sure I do!
Wanna see?
Ah!
So sorry!
I'll make some for you now.
There's no need to hurry!
Crona, now's your chance.
Yeah, right.
What are you waiting for, you moron?
Do you take sugar?
How about some pepper?
I like it spicy.
Oh, okay.
Whatever you say.
Sorry for the wait.
Now then,
let's pick up where we left off, shall we?
You were getting ready to tell me something,
weren't you, Crona?
Oh.
What is it?
Oh, it's nothing.
Okay, if you're sure.
So, Crona,
you wanted to talk?
Thank you, but
I'm much more
r-r-r-r-relaxed now.
Really?
Well, I don't know what was wrong,
but I'm glad you're feeling better.
It's getting late.
I should be going home.
Oh.
Stop by any time.
Beep, beep.
That went smoothly.
Hold on a second, Crona.
What is it?
Is something wrong?
Your pen.
You almost forgot it.
Here.
Goodbye.
See ya.
Be careful on your way back home.
Oh.
How'd it go?
Did you do it?
I'm home.
Welcome back, Stein.
Ribbit.
You hear that?
We've got him.
I'm impressed.
How were you able to get Marie to drink it?
It was easy.
While she was out of the room,
we just added a little drop to her tea.
The magical snake, Marie drank, contain more than a listening device.
It will also speed up the spread of Stein's madness when he's near her.
Crona dropped by just now.
Oh?
Is something wrong?
He doesn't seem to be used to life at the Academy yet, and I can tell it's bothering him.
But he's a good kid.
So sweet and quiet.
Not even suspicious.
What an idiot.
I'm sure he'll be fine.
He'll adjust to this new life at his own pace.
Crona and all the other students are what make teaching at the Academy worthwhile.
It's getting late.
I'm going back to my room now.
Oh.
Crona?
Medusa will be proud of you for doing so well.
Oh.
I don't know.
Excalibur.
From the United K, I'm looking for heaven.
I'm going to California.
Excalibur.
On the next episode of Soul Eater, The Legend of the Holy Sword 3, the Academy Gang Leaders' tale.
How lame.
Excalibur.
Aleba!